https://www.bcteal.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
BC TEAL is committed to protecting the privacy of its members, employees, and other individuals with which it interacts. This policy was developed in compliance with British Columbia’s Personal Information Protection Act (PIPA) and outlines how we manage your personal information.
What is Personal Information?
Personal information means any information about an identifiable individual, such as someone’s name, home address, credit card information, social insurance number, gender, income or family status.
Scope
This policy applies to personal information under BC TEAL’s control or within its custody.
Consent
BC TEAL will seek your consent for the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information, notwithstanding the limited exceptions identified under PIPA.
You may withdraw the consent you provided to BC TEAL for the collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information with the exception if it would interfere with a legal obligation.
Collection
BC TEAL will only collect your personal information when it is needed for legal or business purposes.
BC TEAL will identify the purpose(s) for which it collects personal information, notwithstanding the limited exceptions identified under PIPA.
BC TEAL will only collect the minimum amount of personal information necessary to achieve the stated purpose of collection.
BC TEAL will only collect your personal information directly from you, notwithstanding the limited exceptions identified under PIPA.
Use
BC TEAL will only use your personal information for the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected or for a consistent purpose.
BC TEAL will always seek your consent if we want to use your personal information for a new purpose, notwithstanding the limited exceptions identified under PIPA.
Protection
BC TEAL will take reasonable security steps to protect your personal information under BC TEAL’s control or within its custody from unauthorized collection, use, and disclosure.
Disclosure
BC TEAL will only disclose your personal information to third-parties if it is reasonable and fulfills the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected.
BC TEAL will only disclose your personal information with your consent, notwithstanding the limited exceptions identified under PIPA.
BC TEAL will seek your consent if we intend to disclose your personal information for a different purpose, notwithstanding the limited exceptions identified under PIPA.
Accuracy
BC TEAL will take reasonable steps to ensure your personal information is kept accurate and up-to-date.
You may edit your personal information by logging into My Account on the BC TEAL website and updating the My Account and Edit My Profile sections.
You may request that BC TEAL corrects any of your personal information under BC TEAL’s control or within its custody.
Access
You have the right to request access to your personal information that is under BC TEAL’s control or within its custody, including how your personal information is being used and whether it has been shared with a third-party – this request can be subject to minimal fee.
Retention
BC TEAL will only retain your personal information for as long as it is reasonably needed for legal or business purposes.
Employee Personal Information
BC TEAL will manage its employees’ personal information in accordance with PIPA’s provisions for establishing, managing and terminating an employment relationship.
BC TEAL Website
BC TEAL will manage personal information collected, used or disclosed through its website in accordance with this privacy policy.
BCTEAL.ORG may also use “cookies” and similar technology to obtain information about your visits to our sites or your responses to e-mail from us – both individually and in aggregated data that does not identify you.These reporting tools tell us the parts of our web sites or e-mails in which you showed an interest or took some action, and help us improve the quality and usefulness of our sites. While cookies help us improve your experience while visiting our sites and customize our communications to the services you may desire, you have the option to block them through your Internet browser or other commercially available software. However, doing so may make some of our sites’ features unavailable to you.
Accountability
Please contact admin@bcteal.org should you have any questions, corrections, concerns, or complaints related to how BC TEAL handles your personal information.
Copyright © 2020 bcteal.org
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Website designed by KIMBO Design
